Hello friends, how are you all?  Today I am going to
discuss about the
best opportunity for working from home from ICICI LD.
So see, today's
work is going to be given to you by the company in two ways.
One can work from home and the other can
work from office, meaning you can go to the office
and work from home.
Watch this video completely.  I am going to
share all the information with you.   First of all, whatever
work is there, it is the
work of a customer care executive.  If I
talk about customer care executive, then his
job is to provide support to the customer.   Let us
assume that if someone has any query or
any information, then he calls the company to ask for that information. The
person who
attends that call and
explains the complete details to us is
called customer care executive.  So an
opportunity is being given to apply for the same post.
Both freshers and experienced can apply because here the
company itself is saying that the experience is from zero to 3 years.
Meaning freshers can also apply.
You will get salary ranging from Rs 1.25 to Rs 3.25 per annum.  And the biggest thing is that
you will get work in Mumbai, Thane, Navi Mumbai.
And the most important point is
that you were given the opportunity to apply for this job two weeks in advance.
A start has been made
and 120 people are being given the opportunity to apply.
And the subcentre point is 30
people have applied.  Many people have
not applied yet.  So do
n't miss this opportunity if you want to get a job, the
total process is insurance sales.
Meaning, you will have to sell the insurance of the company
and then
both freshers and expats can apply.
You will get a monthly salary of Rs 16,000 to Rs 18,000 for this work along with
unlimited incentives.  Incentive
means you will be given a target.
When you fulfill that target, the
company will give you incentives.
Remember this and at the same time,
you will get work here in Navi Mumbai locations for those who
want to go and work in offices.  So the minimum qualification should be HS
pass and you are
given Kunal's number of HR level here.
You have to contact this number and know all the details
and after that you have to send your CB also
on this WhatsApp number and the company
itself will inform you about the interview,
when will the interview take place, you will get to know all the details
on this contact number.  Now
look, this work is in BPO categories.  There
is work on voice process and
you will get full time and permanent work.  So
some skills are required for this.
Like you should have knowledge about telecalling, insurance sales
, customer support, sales, health
insurance, life
insurance.  Only then will
you be able to do the work in this manner.
So I have shared this complete details data
with you.  Go
check it out.
I got this work opportunity through ncry.com platform
which I am sharing with you.
I will provide this link below.  Go ahead and
click on apply and
follow me to get updates like this.  Thank you.